Imagine a future where our streets are filled with ads 200m tall; where billboards change before our eyes to give us personalised messages; and where companies track our every move as we walk through a city, pinging our phones with special offers as we near their shops.
想象一下这样的未来：我们的街道上充斥着高达200米的广告；广告牌在我们眼前变换，并提供个性化的信息；当我们在城市中穿行时，公司会追踪我们的一举一动，当我们靠近它们的店铺时，就会向我们的手机发送特价优惠的信息。
In fact, all of these forms of advertising are already being tested.
事实上，所有这些形式的广告都已经在测试中了。
Let‘s take the first of these ideas.
我们先来看看第一个设想。
Back in 1982, science fiction movie Blade Runner envisaged a futuristic cityscape where giant adverts stretched the full height of skyscrapers.
早在1982年，科幻电影《银翼杀手》就设想了一个未来的城市景象，在那里巨大的广告延展到整个摩天大楼的高度。
And UK company Lightvert are now doing something very similar; with one crucial difference.
英国公司Lightvert现在也在做类似的事情，不过有一个关键的区别。
Instead of making immense physical adverts, their commercials are beamed straight into consumers’ eyes.
他们没有制作巨大的实体广告，而是将广告直接投射到消费者的眼睛里。
They do this by attaching a strip of reflective material to a wall, and then projecting an image onto it.
他们通过在墙上贴一条反光材料，然后将图像投射到上面来实现这一点的。
The image then ‘bounces‘ out.
然后这个图像就会“反射”到外界。
You can see it when you walk directly in front of it.
当你直接从图像前面经过时，你就能看到它。
It looks huge and suspended in mid- air, but no one else can - you can only see it from one specific spot.
它看起来巨大且悬浮在半空中，但其他人看不到——只有在一个特定的位置才能看到。
Lightvert claims this form of advertising is unobtrusive and that it can “unlock” vast amounts of “high- value advertising real estate”.
Lightvert公司声称这种形式的广告不引人注目，并且能够“解锁”大量的“高价值广告不动产”。
But not everyone is sold on the idea of living in a world of endless ads.
但并不是每个人都赞同生活在一个充斥着无尽广告的世界里。
In Moscow, for example, a new form of advertising targeting motorists has split opinion.
例如，在莫斯科，一种针对司机的的新型广告引发了意见分歧。
Drivers approaching a particular digital billboard in the city are shown adverts for a new kind of Jaguar car, but only if you are driving a different make of vehicle.
当驾驶员接近城市中某个特定的数字广告牌时，会看到一个新型捷豹汽车的广告，但前提是你驾驶的是其他品牌的车辆。
Sensors in the billboard detect what kind of car you are driving, and send you an ad based on that information.
广告牌中的传感器会检测你驾驶的汽车类型，并根据该信息向你发送广告。
While this may seem invasive, it’s actually the safety aspect that has concerned some observers.
虽然这可能看起来具有侵扰性，但实际上一些观察人士担心的是安全方面的问题。
Researchers in Sweden have shown that digital billboards attract our eyes for longer than other kinds.
瑞典的研究人员已经表明，数字广告牌吸引我们目光的时间比其他类型的广告牌更长。
In fact, they distract us for over two seconds, a length of time which studies have proved to be dangerous on the roads.
事实上，它们会让我们在道路上分心超过两秒钟，而研究已经证明，这个时长是很危险的。
Finally, we have “proximity marketing”, where shops detect where you are on the high street and send tailored adverts to your phone.
最后，还有“近距离营销”，即商店会检测你在商业街的位置，并向你的手机发送定制的广告。
Devicescape is one company trialling the use of Wi-Fi as a means of tracking customers.
Devicescape这家公司正在试验用Wi-Fi作为追踪顾客的手段。
Their technology could work anywhere, whether in “a supermarket, a concert hall, or a bus,” says Owen Geddes from their marketing team.
他们营销团队的欧文·格迪斯表示，他们的技术可以在任何地方使用，无论是“在超市、音乐厅还是公交车上”。
What would customers see?
顾客会看到什么呢？
“It could be a discount offer to use in the shop the person is visiting, or a piece of content such as a movie trailer,” says Mr Geddes.
格迪斯先生说：“可能是在顾客正在光顾的商店里使用的打折优惠，或者是像电影预告片这样的内容。”